lingscars.com 2015-09-27

# CAR LEASING CHEAP NEW UK CARS FOR LEASE CONTRACT HIRE CAR LEASING

|  **LINGsCARS.com LTD Privacy Policy**  
---  
  
HaHaHa! Bugger me! If you are reading this then you must be REALLY worried about your privacy, well... don't worry!

Overview

"New easyJet hostess"

Look, LINGsCARS.com has been trading profitably for donkey's years and I have never once had a serious complaint about someone's privacy. Apart from that nude photo of the easyJet air hostess I published, but that was totally accidental. Michael O'Leary liked that one. However, it pays not to be too paranoid. Certain things are NOT really private, they are semi-public.

Public information

I always hold your information very securely, but some information is out in the open and already public.

For instance, your address is generally public, is broadcast on the voter's roll and is probably sitting there on Google. Anyone who wants to find you can find you. Your car is parked outside your house, so your reg number is hardly a state secret. 100 Spotty and drug-abusing pond-life youths pass your house every day, and glance in your windows. Your bank details... well you give them away, including your bank account name and number, every time you write a cheque. If I were to root through your dustbin, I would figure your chocolate cake fetish. So you have to be a bit sensible.

"Personal documents are kept private!"

Being sensible

If you use me to get a new car, we will have to share loads of "private" information and from my point of view I do a hell of a lot of work to keep all of that stuff private and hidden. But nothing in life is perfect, and you can never remain _"the invisible man"_.  
Or woman.

Applying for a car

If you're applying for a car, I do have to pass your info to a finance company and also (probably) to a car dealer. Car dealers are hopeless. So, while I keep your information securely on a locked-down server at LINGsCARS, other people at finance companies and car dealers may not be so careful and it probably ends up printed on a bit of paper lying on their desk. Finance companies and car dealers are like that.

Private information

Most of your "private" information is available to all via a credit search. I never carry out these credit searches myself, but a finance company certainly will, if you apply for a car. It's no good asking me what's on your credit profile, because I can't see it. But if you want me to guess, I will. If you are particularly persistent, I will make up some fantastic stories about you that will stop you clicking "send" to me, ever again.

Collection of Information

"I keep all information about Duncan Bannatyne's ice cream van private"

LINGsCARS.com holds and stores certain information about you. For example, your breast size, your blood group, your HIV status... **_no, I don't, really._**

I actually hold information related to your visit to this site (such as which pages you visit, how often you visit, where you come from and information you specifically provide to enable you to receive a particular service). But this is all sensible stuff I need in order to make the site work and to give 99.9% of visitors the interactive, enthralling experience they want. Most people would not be able to make head or tail of this rubbish if they tried. Nevertheless, it exists so I tell you about it.

Use of Information Collected

I will only use the information you provide me to process customer orders, get you a car, to send you information you have requested and to help me develop the site to be more useful to you. If you don't want me to tell anyone you have requested a badge, or played my quiz, or scratched your arse, then don't do those things. This is a fairly communicative website. On LINGsCARS, I interact with people. I don't try to embarrass people... but on the other hand, I have fun and we all join in. You are ordering a new car, no-one dies.

Non-personal data may also be used and stored with other persons.

I do not sell or transfer any personal information outside LINGsCARS.com other than where explicit reference is made and approval obtained from you when you provide the information, or where passing that information to third parties is necessary to provide you with the information or service requested. I would love to sell it, because I would make a fortune out of it - but I don't. I put it all on a compost heap called "old data" and I sit on it. Eventually, worms eat it.

Data Protection

LINGsCARS.com has adopted a policy of occasional compliance with the data protection laws of the United Kingdom and takes reasonable care to prevent any unauthorised access to your personal data. Actually, I take great care to prevent any unauthorised access to your personal data, but that sounds pious and self-congratulatory. Also, I'm asking for trouble if I say that I do fantastic things better than most, so I restrict myself to the modest claim of "occasional compliance" and "reasonable care".

"Oh god, not my privacy policy AGAIN..."

If you want to know exactly what information LINGsCARS.com holds on you, you can obtain it by requesting a Subject Access Request Form from LINGsCARS.com at its registered office. A fee will be payable for such access. I have set the fee at £999.99 (including VAT), because, frankly, it will take me weeks to get it all together and I want to make a few quid from you.

By supplying me with information, you confirm that you do not consider use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Statement to be a breach of any of your rights under the Telecommunications (Data Protection and Privacy) Regulations 1999. Or your human rights. By entering information on forms or providing me with any personal information you are consenting to me processing that data for my own business use and holding it on my server. The problem with all these clauses in this Privacy Policy (and others) is that you never read them before you use my website, which is both stupid and sensible. It's stupid because you are giving away all your rights, but sensible because if you read every Privacy Policy you would never have time to surf the web or view any porn. Time is money!

Police and MI5 requests

You should also be aware that if the police or any regulatory or governmental authority investigating suspected unlawful activities demands me to provide your personal details and/or information concerning your activities whilst visiting this site, I shall do so grumpily (however, if we were in China I would think twice about this, as you might end up being shot). If the forces of evil want to know anything about your use of porn, I will stall them as long as possible before grassing you up, completely. Having said that, I have never been approached by MI5 with a demand for your Top 10 Pussy Flick information, so don't worry.

How do I keep your information secure?

"My tank of last resort"

Despite all the rubbish above, LINGsCARS.com takes the security of your personal data very very **_Seriously_** with a capital "S", bold and underline. I use industrial security software to safeguard your data and I also own a Browning machine gun and a small tank. I never sell your information or pass it to anyone other than finance proposal companies and supplying dealers.

I hope you feel you can trust me. If you've read this far, you deserve a free car, and an aspirin as big as a dustbin lid! I do my best. Other Privacy Policies mean absolutely nothing and are full of shit! So I hope you appreciate my honesty  
 _\- Ling_

|   
---  

_I am the Viz UK business ambassador!  
Post me Ferrero-Rochers! Yum Yum!_  
  
**Unlike most other internet car leasing sites, I publish all my contact information openly!  
 _...so, you know who I am_** \- Ling

 **THE UK's **FAVOURITE**  
CAR LEASING WEBSITE!**

**Boss:** Ling Valentine MSc IoD  
LING World Headquarters  
Vance Business Park  
Gateshead, **NE11 9NE**  
Tel 0191 460 9444  
Fax 0870 486 1130  
 _ **I prefer email to phone**_ \- Ling  
VAT No: 866 0241 30  
Co Reg No: 6178634  
Consumer Credit Licence: 663330  
Data Protection No: Z1098490  
Best Before: 17/08/2007  

**Latest BBC NEWS from LING in CHINGLISH!**

**LATEST:  ** _A year after Membling Partiamentary expense cheaters gave green light for bloody annoying Blitish to bomb Islamic State group, lah, Bloody Bloardcasting Corporation defence correspondent Jonathan Beale joins RAF surveillance mission and examines what impact strikes having had. I read you little red book!_ \- news replorted 13:11

**LATEST:  ** More than dozen migrants trying to reach Greece drown after their boat sinks off Turkish coast. Pass chopsticks!!  \- news replorted 13:05

_Former deputy prime dodgy minister John Prescott has offered male gender human bleing's advice to Labour leader Jeremy Corbyn when bloody man is admitted to Privy Council. You understanning yet? Paying more attention!_ \- news replorted 13:00

**Anti-gentrification protesters attack shops and businesses including cafe selling cereal in east London. Sweet sour chicken feet time!** \- news replorted 12:55

_**Facebook founder Mark Zuckerberg announces plans to bring internet to refugee camps, lah, as part of campaign for universal connectivity. You give me happy happy luck luck.** _ \- news replorted 12:48

Volkswagen had warnings about illegally cheating in emission tests years ago, lah, German media cite internal inquiry as saying. No spitting in damn website!!!  \- news replorted 12:47

_**Two teenage boys arrested in connection with fire at mosque complex in south London. Sweet sour chicken feet time!** _ \- news replorted 12:37

**A Great Satan man sets petrol pump on fire as bloody man attempts to burn spider on side of male gender human bleing's car. Hahahaha! Laughing like bloody hell!** \- news replorted 12:25

_Michael Fassbender has described playing Macbeth by imagining him as man suffering from post-traumatic stress. Eating rice!!_ \- news replorted 11:51

**Province of Engrish running-dogs panicked under pressure in their 28-25 funny shape ball-game World Cup loss to Wales, lah, says Welsh land of sheep and more sheep legend Sir Gareth Edwards. Eating rice!!** \- news replorted 11:25

_**One year since bloody annoying Blitish began combat missions against Islamic State militant targets, lah, BBC's Jonathan Beale is first journalist to join RAF Sentinel spy plane crew carrying out surveillance over Iraq and Syria. Ai-yaa!!!** _ \- news replorted 11:21

Visitors to Banksy's Dismaland being invited in to pop-up "bemusement park" (Ai-yaa!!! Bloody Bloardcasting Corporation quotee-quotee!) for final clock time result later. Hahahaha! Laughing like bloody hell!  \- news replorted 10:31

_**The victims of Clutha helicopter tragedy to be commemorated at annual memorial service (???) I wan' service , I wan' you tellibly lovely custlingmer give me damn velly damn good service for old bill bobbys officers who having died while on duty. You give me happy happy luck luck.** _ \- news replorted 10:01

**Great Britain's Johanna Konta beats Andrea Petkovic 6-4 7-5 at Wuhan Open to claim (always claiming, huh?) flemale human person's 19th win in 20 matches. Eating rice!!** \- news replorted 09:48

_Two women and man killed on quad bike when it collides with LINGsCARS (tm) vehicling driving car machine on main road; highway No.16 from Shanghai to Chengdu in West Yorkshire. What the hell I mean??!!_ \- news replorted 09:38

**Britain's Liam Phillips wins BMX Supercross World Cup to become first man to claim (always claiming, huh?) back-to-back titles. Eating rice!!** \- news replorted 09:34

_**Lewis Hamilton defends male gender human bleing's "close" (Ai-yaa!!! Bloody Bloardcasting Corporation quotee-quotee!) pass of Merceding-Blend team-mate Nico Rosberg after winning Japanese Grand Prix.** _ \- news replorted 08:53

Iran's supreme leader calls for Saudi Arabia to apologise for Thursday's Hajj stampede which killed 769 people, lah, adding to raft of criticism by Tehran. Sweet sour chicken feet time!  \- news replorted 08:39

_**The Lake District is one of most beautiful parts of UK, lah, but what is supposed to be feast for eyes is in danger of becoming eyesore. What the hell I mean??!!** _ \- news replorted 08:36

**On last day of Pope Francis' trip to US, lah, million human bliengs expected to gather in Philadelphia to hear Pontiff hold male gender human bleing's final Mass. Eating rice!!** \- news replorted 08:23

_Russia and Estonia exchange two men convicted of spying over bridge separating countries. Eating rice!!_ \- news replorted 08:12

**France says it has carried out its first air strikes against Islamic State militants in Syria** \- news replorted 08:01

_**Mercedes return to front of Formula 1 as Lewis Hamilton wins Japanese Grand Prix to put stranglehold on title race. What the hell I mean??!!** _ \- news replorted 07:45

Banksy's Dismaland has been shot in arm for Weston-super-Mare, lah, attracting thousands of human bliengs to town. Sweet sour chicken feet time!  \- news replorted 07:43

_**Mark Tuffney, lah, head of Lowther Primary in Barnes, lah, says schools meals should be extended, lah, not cut back. What you wan'?!!** _ \- news replorted 07:00

**More than 40 leading health professionals having signed garbling written down on paper message calling on government not to scrap free school meals for infants in Province of Engrish running-dogs. I read you little red book!** \- news replorted 06:58

_Cuts to free school meals for infant pupils could harm children's health, lah, say experts in garbling written down on paper message to newspaper. Hahahaha! Laughing like bloody hell!_ \- news replorted 06:00

**Pope Francis has attended Festival of Families in Philadelphia in Pennsylvania - male gender human bleing's last stop on male gender human bleing's six-day Great Satan tour. Hahahaha! Laughing like bloody hell!** \- news replorted 05:21

_**Nobukazu Kuriki, lah, climber who lost nine of male gender human bleing's fingers to frostbite, lah, abandons male gender human bleing's attempt to reach summit of Mount Everest. Pass chopsticks!!** _ \- news replorted 05:13

Australia warns Great Satan singer Chris "Dear Leader" Brown that bloody man will be denied entry for planned tour of country, lah, because of male gender human bleing's record of domestic violence. What the hell I mean??!!  \- news replorted 05:08

_**Catalonia is due to vote in regional elections that nationalist parties hope will set them on road; highway No.16 from Shanghai to Chengdu to independence from Spain. Sweet sour chicken feet time!** _ \- news replorted 02:33

**David Cameron will call for new diplomatic controlling in driving manner to end Syria's civil fighty bang-bang as bloody man meets world leaders at United Nations in New York. What you wan'?!!** \- news replorted 01:50

_As Super-Duper-Chinese-State President Xi Jinping meets President "I da man! Yes I can!" Obama in Washington, lah, how badly is China's economy stumbling, lah, and what could be impact?_ \- news replorted 01:03

**Welsh land of sheep and more sheep produced performance of belief, lah, guts and fight to beat Province of Engrish running-dogs side undone by 'brain freeze', lah, says Tom Fordyce. What the hell I mean??!!** \- news replorted 00:59

_**Super-Duper-Chinese-State President Xi Jinping pledges to establish $2bn (�RMB Yuan #1.3bn) ni ni ni ni Hao, lah, Zai-Jian! fund to assist developing countries and to cancel debt for least developed nations. Eating rice!!** _ \- news replorted 00:48

Why India's Goa wantings its British tourists back  \- news replorted 00:36

_**How dog helped discover 'kiss of life' technique** _ \- news replorted 00:31

**Sunday's papers look forward to forthcoming Labour party conference, lah, with bloody velly mixed bag of headlines. Eating rice!!** \- news replorted 00:27

_Examining impact of "art phenomenon of 2015" (Ai-yaa!!! Bloody Bloardcasting Corporation quotee-quotee!)_ \- news replorted 00:22

**The sheer joy of doing same thing over and over again** \- news replorted 00:21

_**The women who came together as their countrymen fought** _ \- news replorted 00:16

Designer and entrepreneur Vidhi Mehta has developed biology kit that helping-helping children become ''citizen scientists'', lah, hunting new antibiotics. Eating rice!!  \- news replorted 00:14  
  
|   
---  
| 

1.4 TFSI 125bhp 5dr  
petrol, man, non-met 

A1 

£237.78

per month, inc VAT 

|   
| 

2.0 TDi Blu... 184bhp 5dr  
diesel, man, non-met 

Golf (Mk7) 

£262.80

per month, inc VAT 

|   
| 

1.6 TDI CR 105bhp 5dr  
diesel, man, met 

Ibiza 

£165.50

per month, inc VAT 

|   
| 

1.0 i 60bhp 5dr  
petrol, man, non-met 

Polo 

£174.61

per month, inc VAT 

|   
| 

1.2 PureTec... 82bhp 5dr  
petrol, man, met 

C4 Cactus 

£221.15

per month, inc VAT 

|   

**Play my ** _brilliant_** motoring quiz!**  
   
**EXTRA CHEAP  
CARS ****HERE**  
 _ **See 30 cheapest cars!**_  

...get a **FREE BADGE!  
** ** _Collectors item - FREE!_**  
 **APPLY NOW!**  
  
|    
  
...don't do lease cars, but if they did, they would be done like this **_\- Ling_**  
  
**Click** to see my **LIVE** lease car customers! **_\- Ling_**  
  
**_PLAY BOTTOM TRUMPS!_**  

**Get my _latest_ EMAIL car updates!**  

**My Nuclear  
Missile Truck**
